If you still haven't heard of the Ninja
Creamy, what are you doing? This thing
is insane. It makes low calorie, high
protein ice cream that is just as
delicious as the real deal. Here are
five of the recipes I made this week to
help me lose fat and build muscle. I
started off with a fall classic pumpkin
spice latte. If you're a pumpkin person,
this one will be right up your alley.
Keeping up with the fall theme, I did
apple pie. This was a cinnamon base with
apple pie filling mixed in. Then I made
an all-time classic chunky monkey. So I
recreated the Ben & Jerry's flavor. This
was a banana base with walnuts and
chocolate chips mixed in. And yes,
before you ask, all these recipes are
already posted on my page. So just check
out my page. They're all up on there.
For this next one, I recreated Wendy's
pumpkin spice frosty, and I think it was
better than the real thing. Then to wrap
it all up, I made a maple creamy, which
if you don't know what that is, it
originated in Vermont. They use their
high quality milk and maple syrup to
make a delicious mix between soft serve
and hard ice cream. And as a New
Englander, I knew I had to make this.
And that's it. Follow me for more
recipes.